Péter Bence Márföldi

Budapest, Hungary

☑ peter.marfoldi@gmail.com | 🌴 marfoldi.hu | 🖸 marfoldi | 🛅 marfoldi





Summary.

Passionate engineer with an emphasis on writing clean, concise, idiomatic code. 8+ years experience specializing in full-stack development and consistently striving to work with my fellow peers make a meaningful impact. Interested learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Experience

Lufthansa Innovation Hub

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Developing applications for partners in the travel industry.

Ascenda Loyalty SOFTWARE ENGINEER

• Implementing tools, services and pipelines to provide data to a booking and loyalty platform.

· Main contributor of a Reporting application that consumes data across multiple services and publishes results to our partners.

BSSN Software (Merck Group)

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

• Developing algorithms, services and CRUD applications to process scientific data.

• Interviewing/onboarding and supporting junior colleagues.

Lambda-Com (WebEye Group)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

· As a member of a scrum team taking part in the development of several web applications for vehicle tracking.

· Developing tools for data verification.

Budapest, Hungary (Remote)

Budapest, Hungary (Remote)

Feb. 2022 - Present

Feb. 2019 - Feb. 2022

Budapest, Hungary (Remote) Nov. 2015 - Feb. 2019

Budapest, Hungary

Jun. 2014 - Nov. 2015

Education

Eötvös Loránd University

MSc in Computer Science

• Specialization in software technology (programming languages & distributed systems).

• Thesis title: Documenting functions automatically by recognizing stereotypes.

Eötvös Loránd University

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

• Specialization in software development.

• Thesis title: A visualization and benchmark tool for sorting algorithms.

Budapest, Hungary

Sept. 2015 - July. 2017

Budapest, Hungary

Sept. 2012 - July. 2015

Skills

Languages Ruby, JavaScript, Java, C++ **Back-end** Rails, Hanami, Sinatra, Spring

Front-end Vue.js, AngularJS, JQuery, HTML5, CSS, JavaFX, Swing

DBs SQL (Postgres), MongoDB

DevOps AWS, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes